HIT IT EXACT
Pour in exactly 2000g of water
and get a great prize!
4117 grams!
4117グラム
2117 grams over!
2117グラムオーバー
How unfortunate!
はい　残念
Look at that!
ほら　見ろっ！だから言ったじゃねえか
I told you that we didn't need the last cup!
最後の一杯要らねえって
You're blaming me?
You're always blaming other people!
うーわ　俺のせいにするんだ
Is there a prize for getting close?
あのこれ前後賞とか
I don't think we're anywhere near the mark.
いや　あっても僕らかすりもしてないですから
You put too much water in! Too much water!
You're the one who added the last cup!
最後のいっぱい入れたのはおめーだろうが！
水量音痴
Something's been off since the beginning of the second semester.
二学期になってから　なんか変だ
First question!
High
Schooler
Quiz
Intense
battles
are here!!
それでは第一問
Which Feudal Era commander became famous...
戦国時代に敵将に塩を送ったことで有名な武将は？
for giving salt to his enemy's generals?
Giving salt?
塩をあげた人？
What kind of old lady was he?
なに？
どこの団地のおばちゃん？
Give up, already.
諦めろ
Summer's long over, fall is ending,
夏はとっくに過ぎ
秋も終わりに差し掛かり
文化祭まで始まったというのに
and the cultural festival has started...
Victory is sweet!
You didn't get a single question right.
お前一問も正解してねえだろ
Kaname-kun ended up getting seven questions in a row.
結局要君が七問連続正解でしたからね
Something's not right...
なんか変だ
Poor Cinderella.
かわいそうに　シンデレラ
Her stepmother and sisters must have bullied her again today.
継母と姉さまに今日もいじめられたんだ
ごめんなさい
Oh, sorry!
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか
What are you looking at?
何よそ見してんだ
Here.
はい
Shun-chan...
春ちゃん　ありがとう
Thanks!
変だ
Something's not right.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ      翻译 景寒筱    日校 慧慧 低音子
总校 AL      时间轴 葛蔓     压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
A single flower blooms in the darkness surrounding our school tonight,
今宵も校舎を包む闇の中に一輪の花が咲く
for it is the origin of my name.
なぜなら　それが私の名の由来だから
トイレの花子さん
Bathroom Hanako-san in the cultural festival!
イン文化祭
超メジャーどころの花子さんですら 自分のものにしてしまう
I'll even make the famous Hanako-san my own.
My appeal is limitless!
俺の魅力は無限だぜ
Hold on, Chizuru-kun.
おっと　千鶴君
I'm quite famous, myself.
有名どころで言ったらこちらも負けてませんよ
Whoa! What is that, Yukki? You look so cool!
おぉー　なんだ祐希
それかっけえ
後お父さんがいれば完璧なんですけどね
It'd be perfect if my dad was here, though, for the eye.
目玉の
The eye?
目玉？
あぁーおいコラッ　今日の目玉はこの花子ちゃんでしょうが
Hey, come on! Everyone's got their eye on Hanako-chan today!
いや　そうじゃなくて
No, that's not what I'm talking about. My dad's really the eye...
うちの父さん、本格的に目玉なんで
Hey, what are you still doing here?
お前らまだこんなところに
Guests will be coming in here soon.
もうすぐ客入ってくんだから
うわっはっはっ！要っち　要っちが
Kanamecchi, Kanamecchi!
笑ってんじゃねえよ
Stop laughing!
誰のせいでこんな格好してると思ってんだ
Whose fault do you think this is?
でもちょっとおいしいでしょう
But don't you think it's a bit fruity?
Not at all.
おいしくねえ
キャー  かつらが
My wig!
Hanako-san, a woman's hair is her life.
花子さん　髪は女の命ですぞ
もう何すんのよ　痛いじゃない
What are you doing? That hurt!
It hurts me to see it, too.
見てるこっちもいてぇから
We're opening the haunted house for business.
じゃ　これからお化け屋敷オープンします
Ghosts, give it your best.
お化けの皆さんよろしく
Come on. Let's hide.
ほら 隠れるぞ
Are we really clumping together like this?
なんだよ　この集まりは
あ 誰か来た
Someone's coming.
What? Where? Where? Where?
Hey, hey... I'm so scared.
ねえねえ　怖い
Just hold on and you'll be fine.
捕まってれば大丈夫だって
Okay.
Ignore them.
あんな無視だ無視
I can't stand the thought of someone using us to further their relationship!
ラブイベントに俺たちを利用しようなんて片腹痛いわ
恋のキューピットじゃなくて、あくまでお化けだからね
We're not Cupid. We're ghosts, you know.
お化けなら脅かせよ
If you're a ghost, then scare them.
Come on. Keep walking.
はいはい　ちゃんと歩いて
That's Yuutan's voice!
この声は悠太
Yuuta!
悠太
ご、ごめんね　私も一緒に来ちゃって
I-I'm sorry I came with you...
Don't apologize. I feel better if there are more people with me in a haunted house...
いえ　お化け屋敷は大勢の方が心強いですから
Yuuta!
悠太
Yuuta.
I'm Hanako-san!
花子さんだぞ
Hey, you shouldn't come here.
You're going the wrong way...
おい ダメだって
こっち逆
It's Kaname-kun!
要君だ
What's with your reaction?
今のリアクションの意味を聞かせてもらおうか
Oh, um... I mean...
いや　あの　あの
Why aren't you wearing your vest?
なんでチャンチャンコ着てないの
I thought this would help me blend into the darkness more.
こっちの方がより闇と一体化できるかなって
祐希君頭いい
Yuuki-kun, you're so smart!
You were pretty scared, Mary.
結構ビビッてたな　メリー
Are you stupid? What's with your outfit?
ばっかじゃない
なにその格好は
I'm so scared!
次の客来たぞ
The next guests are coming!
You guys should go.
お前ら早く行け
Okay.
はい
I'm off, too.
俺も行く
Me, too!
花子も行く
おめらはお化けだろうが
You guys are the monsters!
Hanako may be a ghost, but she's also a girl.
花子は幽霊である前に一人の女なのよ
I don't know about that.
知らねえよ
ろくろ首ってマイナー過ぎない？
Don't you think rokurokubi are too obscure to be here?
I don't want to hear it.
余計なお世話です
あ　すみません
Sorry.
メリー　怖くても途中で泣くなよ
Mary, even if you're scared, try not to cry.
W-What are you talking about?
な、何言ってんの
A haunted house like this is too silly to be scary!
このくらいのお化け屋敷おもしろくてつまんないくらいよ
I see.
It's dark! It's scary! No more!
暗いし怖いし
もうやだ
Masaki-chan, are you okay?
茉咲ちゃん大丈夫ですか
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
うん　大丈夫
一緒に行きましょう
Let's go together.
O-Okay.
う、うん
Is the exit still far from here?
出口まだですかね
早く明るいところに出たいよ
I want to get out of this dark place.
We're almost there.
もうすぐですよ
Okay.
はあ　やっと外に出れた
We finally made it out.
Wasn't it scary?
怖かったですね
Yeah, but it was fun.
うん　でも楽しかった
眩しい
So bright.
Ow!
痛い
何　なんで今俺叩かれた
What? Why'd you slap me?
Why were you holding my hand?!
Haunted House
何私の手握ってのよ
Pervert! That's harassment!
変態　セクハラ
What? That's ridiculous!
タコ　抜かしてんじゃねえぞ
You grabbed my hand!
おめえが勝手に握ってきたんだろうが
I never would've done that if I'd known it was yours!
あ、あんたの手って分かってたらしてないわよ
I missed my chance!
もう　トキメキ損よ
かわいくねえ
So not cute.
What's her problem? I was just trying to...
んだよ　せっかくちょっと
Say cheese.
Culture Festival
Culture Fe..
はい　撮ります
ちょっと何？
Wait, what?
What do you mean, "What"?
何って何が？
何言ってんの君たち
What are you two talking about?
はぁ、本当に戻って来ねえつもりか　あいつら
Do they really have no intention of coming back?
あーあ、早く担当時間終わんねえかな
I hope my shift ends soon.
Sis, you're screaming way too much.
ちょっとお姉ちゃん叫びすぎ
Another customer.
また客か
Here we go.
よっこらせった
Re... ve... n... ge...
うーらーめーしーい
That was great!
もう最高
Shut up!
うっせえな
Stop laughing, Hisako!
いつまでも笑ってんじゃねえよ　日紗子
つーか　なんでいきなりくんだよ
What are you doing here?
Damn, this sucks.
くそ　最悪だ
でも本当に似合うね
That look really suits you.
No, it doesn't!
似合わねえから
You're taking it off?
なに　取っちゃうの
It's fine. It's about the end of my shift...
いいんだよ　そろそろ交替の時間だし
Really? Do you have some time after this?
本当　じゃこの後時間ある
なんで？
Why?
Do you want to walk around with us?
よかったら一緒に回らない
私と日紗子ちゃんだけだと迷っちゃいそうで
We'll get lost by ourselves.
Sure.
いいけど
Hey, aren't you in the Student Council?
ねぇねぇ　あんた生徒会入ってんでしょう
Can you get us to the front of all the lines?
順番待ちのところとか顔パスできないの
No.
できねえよ
Kaname-kun, you're in the Student Council?
要君生徒会入ってるんだ
Yeah.
おぉ、まあ
That's amazing!
すごいね
It's nothing, really.
別にそんなでも
It's amazing. It's really amazing.
すごいよ　すごいな
Fine, it's amazing.
じゃ　すごいんじゃないですか
着替えて来る
I'm going to get changed.
Homare High School
Chocolate Bananas
That's a pretty long line.
結構並んでるね
Yakisoba and chocolate covered bananas are the best part of a festival.
焼きそばとチョコバナナは祭りの花だからな
Um, excuse me?
もしもーし
Hey! Don't ignore me!
ほら　無視してんじゃないよ
割り込むなって言ってんの
Don't cut in line.
Huh? Are we lining up from shortest to tallest?
これもしかして背の順なの
No!
違うわ
じゃあいいじゃん
Then who cares?
I care!
いくねえだろう
Go to the end of the line!
さっさと後ろに
Chizuru, if you get in a fight with people who aren't even students while you're looking like that,
千鶴　その格好で一般客に絡むと要に怒られるよ
Kaname will get mad at you.
I'm not starting a fight!
絡んでんじゃねえ
I'm just telling off this rude—
俺はマナーの悪い輩を
Kou-chan!
晃ちゃん
あ、おい　待て
Hey, wait!
"Kou-chan?"
晃ちゃん
東先生の知り合い？
He knows Azuma-sensei?
I dunno.
知らねえよ
なんなんだ　あいつ
Who does he think he is?
頼もう
Fairy Tale Cafe
Excuse me!
Yuutan, Shun-chan!
悠太　春ちゃん
Oh, you came to visit!
遊びに来てくれたんですね
もちろんでしょう
Of course.
午後からお店に立つって言ってたから
We've been looking forward to it, since you told us you'd be working this afternoon.
楽しみにしてたんだよ
それにしても二人ともかわいい
But really, you two look so cute!
そうですか
Really?
Yuuta, you're beautiful.
悠太きれい
Are you Little Red Riding Hood?
これ赤ずきんちゃん
Yes.
はい
Somehow, I can vividly picture you being eaten by a huge wolf.
なんか春ちゃんだと狼に食べられちゃうっていうのが
急に生生しく思えてくるね
はい？
What?
Snow White, if you're not careful,
白雪姫も気を付けないと
you know, a very vindictive person will bring something poisoned to kill you.
ほら、執念深―い人が毒リンゴ持って殺しに来ちゃうよ
Well, I turn away all door-to-door salespeople.
いや　訪問販売は基本門前払いだから
話すら聞かないから
I don't even listen to what they have to say.
意外にしっかりしてるんですね
You're surprisingly level-headed.
Of course I am.
当り前だよ
伊達に一国の姫にやってないよ
I'm not a princess for nothing.
僕、妖精の森ジュース持ってきますから
Sit down and I'll bring you some Fairy Forest juice.
座っててください
Okay.
うん　あり？
Huh?
So you're here, too.
メリーもいたのか
何読んでだよ
What are you reading?
Why do you care?
いいでしょう　別に
セリフの練習してたんだよ
She's practicing her lines.
茉咲のクラス
Masaki's class is performing Cinderella this evening.
夕方からシンデレラの劇やるんだって
へぇー、何役なの　メリー
Really?
What part are you playing, Mary?
A mouse.
ネズミ
What's so funny?
何がおかしいのよ
It's just that you're the perfect size!
だってサイズぴったり
In case you didn't know,
言っとくけどね
ネズミって落ち込んだシンデレラを元気付ける
the mouse has the important job of cheering up Cinderella.
重要な役なんだから
Is that so?
そうだっけ
それで　セリフも覚えたの
Have you already memorized your lines?
当ったり前でしょう
Of course I have.
I've absolutely perfected them.
もうセリフなんて完璧
あ　血出てるぞ
You're bleeding.
本当にドジだな　お前は
You're so clumsy.
ドジじゃないし
I'm not clumsy.
どうしたんですか　千鶴君
What's wrong, Chizuru-kun?
I-It's nothing. Nothing at all.
なんでもないの　なんでも
I'm not clumsy or anything.
ドジなんかしてないの
But...
でも
Ah, I need to go get ready for the play!
私そろそろ劇の準備しないといけないから行くね
ごちそうさま
Thanks for the food.
Masaki-chan...
茉咲ちゃん
Huh?
はい
Break a leg. I'll definitely come see your play.
頑張って下さいね
劇　絶対見に行きますよ
Really?
ほん　本当？
Yes.
はい
You And I
ああ…じゃねえよ
Like hell!
What's wrong with Mary? She's not cute at all!
なんだよ　メリーのやつ
ホンットかわいくねえな
I was only trying to put a band-aid on her cut!
絆創膏巻いてやろうとしただけじゃんかよ
How nostalgic.
でも懐かしいな
僕も初めて茉咲ちゃんに会った時
Masaki-chan got mad at me the first time I met her, too.
怒られたな
絆創膏あげようとしたら
When I tried to give her a band aid,
she said she didn't need my help and ran away.
余計なお世話だって逃げられっちゃって
Huh? That happened to you?
春ちゃんでもそんなことが
本当あれだな
She really doesn't appreciate the kindness of others!
あいつは人の親切は
But when I chased her down and tried to give it to her again, she took it.
でも追いかけてもう一回渡したら
ちゃんともらってくれましたから
What? You chased her?
えっ　追いかけた
I was rather persistent.
しつこかった　ですよね
What's wrong with that?
や　いいんじゃない
Our shifts should be over soon.
そろそろ交替かな
Okay.
はい
That's amazing.
やー　すごいね
Any normal person wouldn't bother chasing her.
普通絶対そこで追いかけられねえよね
だってさ
I mean...
Maybe that's why she likes Shun-chan.
だから春ちゃんなのかな
Chizuru.
千鶴
Huh?
Shouldn't we change before we go see the play?
劇見に行く前に着替えた方がいいじゃないかって
Yeah, yeah!
Where's Kaname-kun?
要君は
I'm sure if you check with the festival committee, they'll understand.
文化祭実行員に確認取れば分かるはずだから
Okay, thanks.
はい　ありがとうございます
He said, "They'll understand."
分かるはずだから　だって
That's the power of the Student Council.
さすが生徒会ね
いちいち反応すんな
Stop saying that.
普通に話してただけだろう
I just talked to her normally.
But you're so composed.
でも落ち着いてるし
私が要君の下級生だったら
If I were your underclassman, I know I'd rely on you.
絶対頼りにしちゃうな
Okay, okay.
いたー
There he is!
Kaname-kun!
要君
What's with you guys?
なんとお前ら
We've been looking all over for you.
もう探したんですよ
You can't ditch the haunted house without saying anything!
勝手にお化け屋敷抜け出すなよ
Why are you still dressed like that?
お前らこそ
なんでまだそんな格好してんだよ
There's no time.
もう時間がない　行きましょう　茉咲ちゃんの劇
Let's hurry to Masaki-chan's play!
はぁ？んなの勝手に行けばいいだろう
Huh? Just go if you want to go.
つーか　お前が一人が行けば十分
In fact, it'll be enough if only you go...
No! Masaki-chan worked really hard on this!
ダメですよ　茉咲ちゃん頑張ったんだから
If we don't all go, I'm sure she'll be disappointed!
皆で見てあげなかったら　きっとがっかりします
いや　お前の鈍感っぷりにがっかりだろうよ
No, I think she'll be disappointed by your stupidity.
Sorry. It looks like you have plans with your friends.
ごめんね　お友達と予定あったんだね
ちげえよ
I don't!
Hello!
は　どうも
I haven't seen you since the fireworks.
花火の時以来ですね
I'm Hanako!
花子でーす
Don't talk to her!
いちいち絡んでくるな
あーダメ　もう着替えてる時間ない
Oh, no. We don't have time to change.
よう！さすがシンデレラ　時間に敏感
Way to go, Cinderella!
Always keeping track of time!
I'm Snow White.
いや　白雪姫だけどね
We don't have time to discuss this!
ってそんなこと話してる場合じゃないですよ
Oh, well! We'll have to go straight there!
しゃねえ　このまま直行じゃ　行くぞ
Let's go!
Hey! Cut it out! I have plans!
おい　やめろって　俺予定が
賑やかね　相変わらず
They're as lively as ever.
いいな
How nice.
カボチャを一つ持って来ておくれシンデレラ
Bring me a pumpkin, Cinderella.
A pumpkin?
カボチャですか
That's right. The biggest one you can find.
あーそうだね　できるだけ大きいのがいい
I understand. I will bring you the biggest pumpkin I can find.
分かりましたわ　おばあさん
This brings back memories. It still smells the same.
懐かしいな　この匂い
変わってないね
There's a good girl. Make haste.
シー　あんまり騒ぐなよ
Don't be so loud.
それより　橘君たちと何話してたんだ
What were you talking to Tachibana-kun and his friends about?
Tachibana? Oh, that short kid?
橘？あー、あのちっこい子？
別に　ちっこいねって言っただけ
I just told him he's short.
You're one to talk.
明も人のこと言えないだろう
同じ年に思われたじゃないのか
He probably thought you were his age.
That's impossible!
そんなことないよ
I'll have to talk to him later.
今度ちゃんと話さないとな
What are you talking about?
なんだよ　それ
お姉さま　やめなさい
Wait, Onee-sama. I didn't mean...
どうしよう　緊張してきた
What am I gonna do? I'm so nervous.
えと　ひとひとひと
Okay, people, underwear, imagine...
Shun-chan said he'd come,
so I have to do a good job.
春ちゃんが見に来るんだから　頑張らなくちゃ
でででも春ちゃんを見たら余計緊張しちゃうかも
B-B-But having him watch makes me even more nervous.
It's okay!
大丈夫よ
With all these people here,
I won't be able to tell where...
お客さん多いから　春ちゃんがどこにいるかなんて
He's right there!
すごく分かる
佐藤さん　出番
Satou-san, we're up!
Okay!
はい
え、えっと　セ、セリフ言わなくちゃ
Um... I-I need to say my l-lines...
えと　かわいそうに　シンデレラ　今日も
Um... Poor Cirerella!
Today...
Her s-stepmother and sisters must have bu-bull-bullied her a-
継母とお姉さまに今日もいじめたれたんだ　ね
-gain.
I really stuttered.
思いっきし噛んだ
Masaki-chan!
茉咲ちゃん
Good work. The play was fantastic...
お疲れ様でした
劇すごく面白かった???
What? Masaki-chan!
茉咲ちゃん
Hey, Mary? Where'd you go?
おーい　メリー
どこ行ったんだ
ったく
Sheesh.
Girls' Bathroom
I can't believe I screwed up such easy lines.
あんな簡単なセリフ間違えるなんて
It was my chance to impress Shun-chan.
せっかく春ちゃんにいいとこ見せるチャンスだったのに
どうしよう　春ちゃんと顔合わせらんない
What am I gonna do? I can't face Shun-chan after that.
Mary?
おい　メリー
Wh-What are you doing in the girls' bathroom?
なななな何、女子トイレに入ってきてのよ　あんたっ！？
What's wrong with Bathroom Hanako-san going in the girl's bathroom?
トイレの花子さんが女子トイレに居ちゃ　おかしいのか？
There's something wrong with your head!
おかしいのはあんたの頭だ
So this is what the girls' bathroom looks like.
へぇー女子トイレってこうなってんだ
Get out!
出てけ
Ow!
いて
You're telling me to get out?
出てけって　お前な
じゃぁ　メリーも出てこいよ
Then you should get out of here, too.
皆探してるぞ
Everyone's looking for you.
What? Is it because you screwed up your lines?
なんだ　セリフ間違えちゃったか
いて　お前な　なんでそうやってすぐ暴力なんだよ　もう
Ow! Why are you so violent?
So you messed up one or two lines...
セリフ間違えの一つや二つなんなよ
あれだぞ
So what? The girl playing Cinderella messed up way more.
シンデレラ役の女子の方が　よっぽどアイタタだったぞ
And she wasn't cute at all.
全然かわいくねえし
Well, it was my own fault for expecting more.
で　変に期待してた俺も俺だけど
おーい　聞いてますか？
Hey, are you listening?
Are-you-lis-ten-ing?
きーいーてーまーすーか
M-My wig!
かつら　かつら被ってみるか
Do you want to try my wig on?
I guess not. I suppose you wouldn't want to.
か、被んねえか　被んねえよな　うん
When...
When I was rehearsing... I could say them.
練習の時はちゃんと言ってた
分かってるよ　そんくらい
I know that.
そんなの劇見てた人、皆分かってる
Everyone watching the play could tell.
Shun-chan knows, too.
春ちゃんだって　ちゃんと分かってる
Did Shun-chan say that?
春ちゃん　そう言ってた？
No, but...
いや　言ってないけど
B-But he knows! Honestly!
けど分かってんの　分かってんの　ちゃんと
But Shun-chan didn't watch me rehearse!
でも春ちゃん　私が練習してるとこ見てないし
He doesn't have to see you to know!
見てなくても分かんの
Don't underestimate a man's imagination!
男の想像力なめんな
But what if he doesn't know?
でも分かってなかったら
He does know! 100%!
だから分かってるって
100パー
He knows!
分かってる
He really does!
本当に
Definitely!
絶対
Okay!
よし
Come on. Let's go.
ほら　行くぞ
Unbelievable.
ったく
You're the only one who'd run to the bathroom.
しかしあれな　トイレに逃げ込むなんてお前ぐらいだぞ
These days, kids go to the roof or the river, Mary-san.
今時のヤングは屋上とか河原に行くもんですよ
メリーさん
Shut up. I don't need that.
うるさいわね
いいわよ
でも　女子トイレまで追っかけて来るのあんたぐらいよ
But you're the only one who'd chase me into the girls' bathroom.
I can't go out looking like this!
この格好はねえだろう　俺
We're really not going out there?
もう　本当に皆出ないんですか
後夜祭出る元気あるなら家帰るから
If I had the energy to go to the dance tonight, I'd go home.
But it'd make a good memory.
いい思い出になるのに
いい思い出なら出来たよな
We've already made plenty of good memories, haven't we, getting-yelled-at Hanako-san?
怒られ花子さん
Shut up!
うるさいわ
Sensei! There's a boy dressed like a girl in the bathroom!
先生　トイレに女装男子が
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
五月蠅い五月蠅い五月蠅い五月蠅い…
When I remember you holding my left hand,
あの時握られた左手を思い出すと
体中が取り合いをして　おなかの辺りがこそばゆくなる
my entire body feels conflicted...
and my stomach tickles.
窓際に流れる光がなぞる君の赤い頬も
Your red cheeks traced by the light pouring through the window...
光をいっぱい乗せて笑うそのまつ毛も
and your brightly smiling eyelashes...
今は全部そのやわらかそうに揺れる髪の向こう側で
are all beyond that soft, wavy hair.
But I end up imagining this and that about being with you someday and...
それなのに
君とのいつかをあれこれ考えちゃったりして
すけべー
Pervert.
千鶴君
Chizuru-kun?
Your attention everyone!
はいはい　皆さん注目
Who wants to know what the girls' bathroom looks like?
女子トイレがどうなってるか知りたい人
A-Are you stupid?
ば　バカじゃないの　あんた
Becoming embarrassed tickled my stomach again.
勝手に照れては
またおなかがこそばゆくなった
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Next time: Crescent Moon Silhouette.
Crescent Moon Silhouette